<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="defaultActivityEntries">
		<item>Home</item>
		<item>Favourite Stops</item>
		<item>Closest Favourite Stop</item>
		<item>Nearby Stops</item>
		<!-- <item>Hunt Down My Trips</item> -->
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="defaultActivityEntryValues">
		<item>HomeActivity</item>
		<item>StopsListActivity</item>
		<item>ClosestStopsListActivity</item>
		<item>NearStopsActivity</item>
		<!-- <item>PredictionActivity</item> -->
	</string-array>

	<string-array name="welcomeMessages">
		<item>Dude, wheres my tram?</item>
		<item>My milkshakes bring all the trams to the stop</item>
		<item>All your tram are belong to us</item>
		<item>Oh Trameo, oh Trameo where art thou?</item>
		<item>Frankly my dear, I dont give a tram</item>
		<item>May the tram be with you</item>
		<item>I love the smell of tram in the morning!</item>
		<item>E.T. tram home</item>
		<item>There's no tram like home</item>
		<item>Say 'hello' to my little tram</item>
		<item>Open the tram bay doors, HAL</item>
		<item>My tram, my precious</item>
		<item>We'll always have trams!</item>
		<item>If you tram it, they will come</item>
		<item>There is no tram</item>
		<item>Here's looking at you, tram</item>
		<item>Snakes on a tram!</item>
		<item>I'm on a tram</item>
		<item>I see your tram is as late as mine</item>
		<item>Tram-a-lama-ding-dong</item>
		<item>I see trams, they're everywhere...</item>
		<item>I can haz my tramz time</item>
		<item>Time stops for no tram</item>
		<item>One small step for trams</item>
		<item>One small step for man, one giant leap for tram times</item>
		<item>You can't handle the tram</item>
		<item>Show me the trolley</item>
		<item>If a tram arrives in a forest and there's no one to board it, does it make a 'ding'?</item>
		<item>Swanston Street is like a box of trams, you never know which one you're gonna get...</item>
		<item>Houston, we have a tram</item>
		<item>Tram on, tram off</item>
		<item>Who let the trams out?</item>
		<item>These are not the trams you are looking for</item>
		<item>If you catch my tram, all of your wildest dreams will come true</item>
		<item>An den? ding. annn den? ding. an den? ding ding</item>
		<item>The first rule of tram club, dont talk about tram club</item>
		<item>Stay away from her you tram!</item>
		<item>Asta la vista Tramy</item>
		<item>If it dings, we can catch it</item>
		<item>He said 'Let there be light rail', and there were trams...</item>
		<item>Catch me if you can...</item>
		<item>A tram for all seasons</item>
		<item>We're going to need a bigger tram</item>
		<item>Do or do not, there is no tram</item>
		<item>Crikey it's a tram, I'll catch it if I can</item>
		<item>Are the trams still screaming</item>
		<item>Silence of the trams</item>
		<item>Wham bam thank you tram</item>
		<item>It ate my tram ticket, doh!</item>
		<item>I'm sorry inspector, I left my tram ticket at home</item>
		<item>Shaken, not tramed</item>
		<item>Tram, James Tram</item>
		<item>You dingin' at me? Are you dingin' at me?</item>
		<item>I know what you're thinking, has he missed 6 trams or only 5?</item>
		<item>Toto I've got a feeling were not on a tram anymore</item>
		<item>What we have here, is a failure to catch a tram</item>
		<item>Play it again tram</item>
		<item>Please tram, I'd like some more</item>
		<item>I like dem french fried trams, mmmmHHhhhmmmm</item>
		<item>You call that a tram? Thats not a tram. This is tram!</item>
		<item>It's going straight to the tram room</item>
		<item>Will you take the red tram or the blue tram</item>
		<item>Is that a tram I see before me?</item>
		<item>I know tram fu</item>
		<item>Never send a man to do a trams job</item>
		<item>Do you feel lucky, tram?</item>
		<item>A good tram is hard to find</item>
		<item>Can you do it on a tram, would you have green eggs and ham?</item>
		<item>To the world you may be one tram, to one tram you may be the world</item>
		<item>Give me liberty or give me trams!</item>
		<item>I am the tram king, I can do anything...</item>
		<item>Absence makes the tram grow fonder</item>
		<item>Float like a butterfly, ding like a tram</item>
		<item>A tram, a tram, my kingdom for a tram</item>
		<item>Hey boy, you're looking mighty cute in that tram</item>
		<item>I pity the tram</item>
		<item>All right, Mr. DeMille, I'm ready for my tram</item>
		<item>Luke, I am your tram</item>
		<item>You'll never know the dark side of the tram</item>
		<item>I ding, therefore I tram</item>
		<item>I had a tram, where all men were created equal</item>
		<item>I really shouldn't have written all of those tram programs</item>
		<item>I'm just a sweet tramsvestite from tramsilvania</item>
		<item>Your daughter came into my yard and kicked my tram</item>
		<item>I always relied on the kindness of passengers</item>
		<item>Trams like turtles</item>
		<item>Loltram</item>
		<item>Because we tram, tram, tram...</item>
		<item>Leave Tramney alone!</item>
		<item>Tramomenom... do doo do do do</item>
		<item>If you cut me, do I not ding?</item>
		<item>Everybody knows, those Trams don't work on water</item>
		<item>I'd ride that for a dollar</item>
		<item>Step away from the tram. You have 20 seconds to comply</item>
		<item>Of all the trams in all the world, you had to walk onto mine</item>
		<item>Yes we tram</item>
		<item>Shot through the heart, and you're to blame, you give trams a bad name</item>
		<item>He's not the messiah, he's a very naughty tram</item>
		<item>Stop, Trammer time</item>
		<item>Trams, no here chopper</item>
		<item>To tram or not to tram, that is the question</item>
		<item>Tram with me if you want to live</item>
		<item>Wham bam thank you tram</item>
		<item>Yabba tramma doo!</item>
		<item>Error 404. Tram not found</item>
	</string-array>

</resources>
